<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Famous BAR</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="tutorial_third">On the map you will find a marker that is the place you must reach. At each place you will get a question about Brno. Sometimes you will have to scan a QR code to get it. Mendel divided a picture of a famous place in 9 parts. You already have one and must reach others. At each good answer, you will get at least one of eight missing parts. Whenever you want, you can check the picture with the parts you have already reached by clicking the button on the bottom right of the map. At the end you will need to find what’s on the picture to get a prize. Anyway, you will get directions to the place which is on the picture even if you don’t find the good answer after 3 tries. At anytime you can reset the game or show the tutorial in the settings.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_second">Do you know Gregor Mendel? Mendel was a scientist born in a German-speaking family in the Silesian part of the Austrian Empire (today’s Czech Republic). He gained posthumous recognition as the founder of the modern science of genetics. Today, a university in Brno is called Mendel University in memory of this great man. Mendel will guide you through the city to discover famous places of Brno which are plenty of history. Swipe right to lean about instructions for the game.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_first">It’s the second largest city in Czech Republic by population and area but also the largest Moravian city and the historical capital city of the Margraviate of Moravia. Brno lies at the confluence of the Svitava and Svratka rivers and has about 400 000 inhabitants. Swipe left to discover your guide for this awesome sightseeing.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_first_title">Welcome in Brno!</string>
    <string name="activity_title_puzzle_image">Pieces of puzzle</string>
    <string name="activity_title_about_us">About us</string>
    <string name="activity_title_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="activity_question_title">Question</string>
    <string name="activity_questions_submit">Submit</string>
</resources>